Guide to the Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
Cornell University College of Engineering Dean's Office records, [ca. 1916-2000]
- S's - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1958 - 1971 (Box 102, Folder 2)
- S, 1972 - 1989 (Box 102, Folder 3)
- Sage Graduate Center, 1961 (Box 102, Folder 4)
- Sailer, James (student), 1979-1981 (Box 102, Folder 5)
- Salaries, 1963-1975 (Box 102, Folder 6)
- Sanitary Engineering Conference, 1969 (Box 102, Folder 7)
- Schwartz, Mark - Staff, 1976-1979 (Box 102, Folder 8)
- Science, Technology, and Society, January 1969-June 1974 (Box 102, Folder 9)
- SCORE (Student Competitions of Relevant Engineering), 1971 (Box 102, Folder 10)
- Sea Grant College Program, 1968-1977 (Box 102, Folder 11)
- Secondary Schools, 1960-1968 (Box 102, Folder 12)
- Secondary Schools Committees, 1957-1963 (Box 102, Folder 13)
- Secondary School Visits, 1958-1962 (Box 102, Folder 14)
- Seminar in Engr. Education 4706 Bolgiano, Conta, Nichols, 1970 (Box 102, Folder 15)
- Seminars - Faculty, 1960-1965 (Box 102, Folder 16)
- Sex discrimination in Education, 1972-1975 (Box 102, Folder 17)
- Sheperd Report, September 1968 (Box 102, Folder 18)
- Shops, 1965-1972 (Box 102, Folder 19)
- Silbert, Joseph, 1975-1987 (Box 102, Folder 20-21)
- Simmons, Ron, 1985-1986 (Box 102, Folder 22-23)
- Sindler Report, 1967 (Box 102, Folder 24)
- S.I.S. or Alternate System, 1975 (Box 102, Folder 25)
- Sinfelt, John H. Dr., 1972 (Box 102, Folder 26)
- Sloan Proposal, 1955-1961 (Box 102, Folder 27)
- Sloan Proposal Final Draft and Presentation, 1964-1965 (Box 102, Folder 28)
- Smith, Howard G., 1982-1983 (Box 102, Folder 29)
- Smith II Report, 1963-1964 (Box 102, Folder 30)
- Snee Hall Dedication 10/8/84 (Box 102, Folder 31)
- Social Science Research Center, 1964-1969 (Box 102, Folder 32)
- Sociology Study Committee at C.U., 1969 (Box 102, Folder 33)
- Soil Mechanics, 1969-1974 (Box 103, Folder 1)
- Space Allocation, 1964-1970 (Box 103, Folder 2)
- Space Science, Graduate Program - Navy, 1958 (Box 103, Folder 3)
- Space Technology Film, 1958-1959 (Box 103, Folder 4)
- Spend to Save Committee, 1977-1978 (Box 103, Folder 5)
- Sperry Hall Dedication, 1966-1975 (Box 103, Folder 6)
- Sporn, Phillip, 1962-1978 (Box 103, Folder 7)
- Sporn, Phillip - American Gas and Electric, 1957-1959 (Box 103, Folder 8)
- Sproull, Robert L., 1965-1981 (Box 103, Folder 9)
- Statistics - College of Engineering, 1959 (Box 103, Folder 10)
- Stallman Estate, 1980-1982 (Box 103, Folder 11)
- Stamp, Neal R., 1977 (Box 103, Folder 12)
- Strategic Defense Initiative (SDI), 1982-1985 (Box 103, Folder 13)
- Streett, W.B., 1982-1986 (Box 103, Folder 14)
- Student Attitudes, 1954-1971 (Box 103, Folder 15)
- Student Council, Engineering, 1979 (Box 103, Folder 16)
- Students - Office of the Dean, 1970-1978 (Box 103, Folder 17)
- Student Organizations, 1957-1966 (Box 103, Folder 18)
- Student Records - Policy on Release of, 1967-1976 (Box 103, Folder 19)
- Student Response System (Kimball Hall), 1971 (Box 103, Folder 20)
- Student Services - Medical, Counsel, etc., 1967-1981 (Box 103, Folder 21)
- Student Support Services, 1977-1978 (Box 103, Folder 22)
- Study of 6-Year Engineering Plan, 1958-1960 (Box 103, Folder 23)
- Subpoena Policy, Univ., 1972 (Box 103, Folder 24)
- Summer 1969 Ad Hoc Study Groups, 1958-1969 (Box 103, Folder 25-26)
- Summer Courses for Faculty, 1966-1967 (Box 103, Folder 27)
- Summer Employment - Students, 1965 (Box 103, Folder 28)
- Summer Institute of Women Engineering Undergraduates, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 29)
- Summer Institutes, 1963-1964 (Box 103, Folder 30)
- Summer Session, 1969-1983 (Box 103, Folder 31)
- Summers, Philip N. ' 76 Memorial Endowment, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 32)
- Sunbeam Corp., 1980 (Box 103, Folder 33)
- Survey Engineering College Program, 1974 (Box 103, Folder 34)
- Swersey, Burt L., 1969 (Box 103, Folder 35)
- Symposium, Technology Ithaca, N.Y., 1969 (Box 103, Folder 36)
- Synchrotron, 10 BEV (Dynamitron), 1961-1966 (Box 103, Folder 37)
- Szekely, J. Professor, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 38)
- Szilagyi, Miklos, 1979-1980 (Box 103, Folder 39)
- T's - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1960 -1971 (Box 103, Folder 40)
- Tape Recording Library, 1957 (Box 103, Folder 41)
- Task Force, Alumni Relations, 1982-1983 (Box 103, Folder 42)
- Task Forces, 1970-1975 (Box 104, Folder 1)
- Task Force on Engineering Legislation, 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 2)
- Tau Beta Pi, 1967-1984 (Box 104, Folder 3)
- Teaching Awards, 1965-1970 (Box 104, Folder 4)
- Teaching, Evaluation of - Ad Hoc Committee, 1967-1971 (Box 104, Folder 5)
- Teaching Machines, 1961-1962 (Box 104, Folder 6)
- Technical Services Act, 1965-1968 (Box 104, Folder 7)
- Technology Assessment, 1969-1970 (Box 104, Folder 8)
- Tech. Challenges in World Market Research Conf., 1964 (Box 104, Folder 9)
- Technology Transfer, 1979 (Box 104, Folder 10)
- Telephones, 1980-1983 (Box 104, Folder 11)
- Television Closed Circuit Project, 1962-1975 (Box 104, Folder 12)
- Tenure, 1972-1985 (Box 104, Folder 13)
- Theoretical and Applied Mathematics, 1962-1989 (Box 104, Folder 14)
- Theory Center, 1986-1987 (Box 104, Folder 15)
- Theory Center, 1985-1987 (Box 104, Folder 16)
- Theory Center, 1985-1987 (Box 104, Folder 17)
- Theory Center Campus Visit 10/30 - 31/87 (Box 104, Folder 18)
- Theory and Simulation Science Center, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 19)
- Theory and Simulation Science Center, 1982-1984 (Box 104, Folder 20)
- Theory Center - UDC Hearing, 1987-1988 (Box 104, Folder 21)
- Thermal Effects Study, 1967-1969 (Box 104, Folder 22)
- Thornfield Conference on Undergraduate Education, 1968-1988 (Box 104, Folder 23)
- Thurston Hall, 1941 (Box 104, Folder 24)
- TIMS, 1971-1972 (Box 104, Folder 25)
- Title IX Summary Report, 1976 (Box 104, Folder 26)
- Todd, Walter L., 1960-1967 (Box 104, Folder 27)
- Remote Sensing, 1978-1984 (Box 105, Folder 1)
- Remote Sensing, 1974-1980 (Box 105, Folder 2)
- Reineman, Howard H., 1978 (Box 105, Folder 3)
- Research, 1980-1984 (Box 105, Folder 4)
- Research, 1961-1978 (Box 105, Folder 5)
- Research Park - Tompkins County Area Development Corp., 1963-1968 (Box 105, Folder 6)
- Research Policies at Cornell, 1964-1966 (Box 105, Folder 7)
- Research Reviews, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 8)
- Reshotko, Eli, 1963-1974 (Box 105, Folder 9)
- Resource Study, NYS (Mortenson, K.E.), 1967 (Box 105, Folder 10)
- Rhodes, F.H.T., President - Engineering College Visits, 1977-1983 (Box 105, Folder 11)
- Rhodes, Frank H.T., 1977-1987 (Box 105, Folder 12)
- Rice, James R., 1973 (Box 105, Folder 13)
- Richards, Timothy, 1969 (Box 105, Folder 14)
- Ridenour, George A., 1978-1979 (Box 105, Folder 15)
- Rochester Gas and Electric, 1963-1970 (Box 105, Folder 16)
- Rockafellor, R.T., 1977 (Box 105, Folder 17)
- Rockwell International, 1976-1979 (Box 105, Folder 18)
- Rockwell International, 1976-1982 (Box 105, Folder 19)
- Tenure, 1968-1972 (Box 105, Folder 20)
- Terman Committee (NYS Study Committee), 1968-1969 (Box 105, Folder 21)
- Terman Committee (NYS Study Committee), 1968-1969 (Box 105, Folder 22)
- Test Bay Space, 1959 (Box 105, Folder 23)
- Texas Trip, December, 1974 (Box 105, Folder 24)
- Theoretical and Applied Mechanics, 1974-1987 (Box 105, Folder 25)
- Theory Center's 1986 Conference - The Univ.-Industry Supercomputer Connection (Box 105, Folder 26)
- Theory Center Quarterly Reports, 1987-1989 (Box 105, Folder 27)
- Theory Center Quarterly Reports, 1986-1987 (Box 105, Folder 28)
- Theory Center, 1988-1989 (Box 105, Folder 29)
- Theory Center, 1987 (Box 105, Folder 30)
- Tompkins County Area Development Corp., 1969-1981 (Box 105, Folder 31)
- Tompkins County Trust Co., 1975 (Box 105, Folder 32)
- Tool Steel Gear and Pinion Company, 1973 (Box 105, Folder 33)
- Torrance, Kenneth (Assoc. Dean Research and Graduate Programs), 1985-1986 (Box 105, Folder 34)
- Tower Club (Box 105, Folder 35)
- Transfers, 1959 (Box 105, Folder 36)
- Transfers - Community Colleges, 1965-1971 (Box 105, Folder 37)
- Patt, Yale - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 1)
- Paul, Charles Kendall - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 2)
- Pearce, Richard A.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 3)
- Pearson, Frank W.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 4)
- Peech, Michael - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 5)
- Pendleton, C.M.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 6)
- Pennock, John C.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 7)
- Pentland, William - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 8)
- Perkins, Harold C.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 9)
- Perkins, Roy B.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 10)
- Perry, John E.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 11)
- Pesce, Gabriel V.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 12)
- Peterson, Harry C.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 13)
- Peterson, Mason Marcus - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 14)
- Pierce, Felix John - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 15)
- Pierlott, Robert George Jr.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 16)
- Pigage, Leo C.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 17)
- Platt, Norval L. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 18)
- Pleuthner, Richard Louis - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 19)
- Poor, Jeanette Alice - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 20)
- Powell, Hugh N.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 21)
- Prada, Guillermo - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 22)
- Priest, Melville S.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 23)
- Purcell, Walter Joseph - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 24)
- Putnam, Abbott Allen - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 25)
- Qian, Jia-Hua - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 26)
- Qian, Yi - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 27)
- Qiu, Freeman Hong-Lie - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 28)
- Quaas, Martha L. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 29)
- Quazi, Abdul - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 30)
- Quick, R.L. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 31)
- Quigley, Gerard Paul - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 32)
- Quinn, Bayard E.- Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 33)
- Quinn, Jerome - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 34)
- Quirke, Nicholas - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 35)
- Rahn, Lloyd N. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 36)
- Rathbun, William Taylor - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 37)
- Raven, Francis H. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 38)
- Reece, John William - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 39)
- Reid, Lincoln - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 40)
- Rettger, E.M. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 41)
- Revelle, Charles S. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 42)
- Reyna, Juan E. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 43)
- Rhodes, Fred H. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 44)
- Richards, William L. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 45)
- Richardson, William B. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 46)
- Richman, Eugene (Box 106, Folder 47)
- Ridley, Brian Kidd - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 48)
- Riparbelli, Carlo - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 49)
- Ritchey, H.W. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 50)
- Robertson, George M. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 51)
- Robinson, David Nelson (Box 106, Folder 52)
- Robinson, Robert E. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 53)
- Rogers, Fred Stillman - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 54)
- Rogers, Gardiner M. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 55)
- Rogers, John Barker III - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 56)
- Rogers, Samuel E. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 57)
- Rooney, John F. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 58)
- Roos, Alfred M. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 59)
- Rose, John L. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 60)
- Rostoker, Norman - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 61)
- Rott, Nicholas - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 62)
- Rubert, Kennedy F. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 63)
- Rubinovitch, Michael - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 64)
- Rudwick, Bernard Herman - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 65)
- Ruhl, Roland - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 66)
- Rumi, Gian-Carlo - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 67)
- Russell, Morell B. Dr. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 68)
- Ryan, Thomas A. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 69)
- Saad, M.A. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 70)
- Sack, Henri S. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 71)
- Salpeter, Miriam - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 72)
- Saltz, Fred - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 73)
- Saltzman, Sidney - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 74)
- Sardi, Otto - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 75)
- Sawdon, Will M. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 76)
- Sawers, Edward H. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 77)
- Sayles, C.I. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 78)
- Scafford, Robert L. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 79)
- Scala, Eraldus - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 80)
- Scattergood, Eugene Robert - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 81)
- Schauss, Stanley Lewry - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 82)
- Schiffmacher, Edward R. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 83)
- Schiller, Edmond J. Jr. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 84)
- Schoder, E.W. - Faculty File (Box 106, Folder 85)
- Transportation Policies - Emerging Urban, 1966 (Box 106, Folder 86)
- Transportation Study, 1964 (Box 106, Folder 87)
- Triangle Fraternity, 1988 (Box 106, Folder 88)
- Triga Reactor, 1980 (Box 106, Folder 89)
- Trustees, Board of, 1980-1986 (Box 106, Folder 90)
- Trustees, Board of, 1975-1980 (Box 106, Folder 91)
- Trustees, Board of, 1966-1975 (Box 106, Folder 92)
- Trustee Committee, Ad Hoc Comm.; Cornell - State Relations (Box 106, Folder 93)
- Tyler, Winfield W., 1973-1974 (Box 106, Folder 94)
- Tuition, 1958-1961 (Box 106, Folder 95)
- Tutoring Program, 1961-1966 (Box 106, Folder 96)
- Material Science and Engineering, 1979-1984 (Box 107, Folder 1)
- Mathematical Sciences Institute, 1985-1991 (Box 107, Folder 2)
- Mechanical and Aerospace Engineering, 1963-1984 (Box 107, Folder 3)
- Mechanical Systems and Design Department, 1971-1975 (Box 107, Folder 4)
- Policy Committee - Degree Programs, 1964-1965 (Box 107, Folder 5)
- Policy Committee - Summary of Responses From Undergraduates, 1977 (Box 107, Folder 6)
- Two - Year Colleges - State University of New York, 1966-1969 (Box 107, Folder 7)
- U's - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1959 - 1971 (Box 107, Folder 8)
- UNESCO, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 9)
- Union at Cornell, 1970 (Box 107, Folder 10)
- United Fund, 1969-1982 (Box 107, Folder 11)
- UNIVAC Computer, 1952-1957 (Box 107, Folder 12)
- University Councils - Annual Report, 1964-1965 (Box 107, Folder 13)
- University Development, 1961-1964 (Box 107, Folder 14)
- University Faculty Dean's Office, 1987-1988 (Box 107, Folder 15)
- University Faculty Dean's Office, 1986-1987 (Box 107, Folder 16)
- University Faculty, 1984-1986 (Box 107, Folder 17)
- University Faculty, 1980-1984 (Box 107, Folder 18)
- University Faculty, 1979-1981 (Box 107, Folder 19)
- University Faculty, 1976-1979 (Box 107, Folder 20)
- University Faculty, 1976-1977 (Box 107, Folder 21)
- University Faculty, 1968-1975 (Box 107, Folder 22)
- University Objectives, 1958 (Box 107, Folder 23)
- University Relations, Office of, 1986-1988 (Box 107, Folder 24)
- University of the State of New York, 1952-1958 (Box 107, Folder 25)
- Urban and Regional Studies Program, 1974-1977 (Box 107, Folder 26)
- V's - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1965 - 1989 (Box 108, Folder 1)
- Vaughn, Henry G. (Box 108, Folder 2)
- Venture Research Program at British Petroleum (Dr. D.W. Braben), 1981 (Box 108, Folder 3)
- Vice President Research, 1986-1989 (Box 108, Folder 4)
- Vice President Research (R.Barker), 1983 - 1984 (Box 108, Folder 5)
- Vice President Research (W. Donald Cooke), 1982 (Box 108, Folder 6)
- Visiting Professors, 1965-1969 (Box 108, Folder 7)
- Visting Scholars, 1958-1963 (Box 108, Folder 8)
- Visual Aids, 1971 (Box 108, Folder 9)
- Wallace Steel and Supply Prize, 1958-1960 (Box 108, Folder 10)
- Ward, J. Carleton, 1984-1985 (Box 108, Folder 11)
- Washington Letters, 1966-1971 (Box 108, Folder 12)
- Waterman, Alan T. Award (NSF), 1981-1982 (Box 108, Folder 13)
- Water Resources and Marine Sciences, 1973-1974 (Box 108, Folder 14)
- Water Resources Engineering, 1965-1970 (Box 108, Folder 15)
- Water Resources Center - Proposals, 1972-1973 (Box 108, Folder 16)
- Weese, John A., Jr. (University of Denver), 1974 (Box 108, Folder 17)
- Weinberg, Alvin, 1973-1975 (Box 108, Folder 18)
- Welch, John F. - CEO, GE; Hatfield Fellow, 1982-1985 (Box 108, Folder 19)
- Wells College Three-Two Program, 1979 (Box 108, Folder 20)
- Westinghouse Electric Company, 1958-1962 (Box 108, Folder 21)
- Westinghouse Microwave Tube Laboratory, 1957 (Box 108, Folder 22)
- "What Size Cornell?", 1959 (Box 108, Folder 23)
- Wheeler, Druid E. III - Memorial Book Fund, 1973-1974 (Box 108, Folder 24)
- White, Richard N., 1985-1987 (Box 108, Folder 25)
- Willers, D.K., 1978 (Box 108, Folder 26)
- Winding, Charles C., 1973-1977 (Box 108, Folder 27)
- Winding/Projects, 1977-1979 (Box 108, Folder 28)
- Winter, George, 1971-1983 (Box 108, Folder 29)
- Winter, George - Testing Laboratory, 1981-1982 (Box 108, Folder 30)
- Women's Caucus, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 31)
- Wood, Colin E.C. Dr., 1981 (Box 108, Folder 32)
- Wood, Frederick F., 1977-1980 (Box 108, Folder 33)
- Wright, T.P. Dr., 1960-1961 (Box 108, Folder 34)
- XYZ - Miscellaneous 1958-1960 (Box 108, Folder 35)
- Yoshikawa, Shoichi Dr., 1967-1974 (Box 108, Folder 36)
- Yu, Charles Y. - Scholarship Fund, 1978 (Box 108, Folder 37)
- Zahorik vs. Cornell University, 1982-1984 (Box 108, Folder 38)
- Zurn, 1970-1971 (Box 108, Folder 39)
- Engineering College Council, 1962-1964 (Box 108, Folder 40)
- Engineering College Council, 1960-1961 (Box 108, Folder 41)
- Engineering College Council - Resolutions for Retired Council Members, 1945-1968 (Box 108, Folder 42)
- Engineering College Council - Biographical sketches of members, 1968-1969 (Box 108, Folder 43)
- Engineering College Council- Comments on Study Report, 1964 (Box 108, Folder 44)
- Sibley School of Mechanical Engineering Report - "The Dept. of Thermal Engineering: Past,Present and Future", April 1961 (Box 108, Folder 45)
- Report for ECC - School of Civil Engineering, November 3-4, 1961 (Box 109, Folder 1)
- Report for ECC - School of Chemical Engineering, April 1962 (Box 109, Folder 2)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 16-17, 1962 (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 24-25, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 4)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 15-16, 1963 (Box 109, Folder 5)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 1-2, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 6)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 20-21, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 7)
- Engineering College Council, November 21-21, 1964 (Box 109, Folder 8)
- Engineering College Council, 1964-1967 (Box 109, Folder 9)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 7-8, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 10)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 5-6, 1965 (Box 109, Folder 11)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 13-14, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 12)
- Engineering College Council, November 18-19, 1966 (Box 109, Folder 13)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 14-15, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 14)
- Engineering College Council Meeting - Cisler Dinner, April 14, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 15)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, October 27-28, 1967 (Box 109, Folder 16)
- ECC Special Meeting, April 12, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 17)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 12, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 18)
- PEW Luncheon and Engineering College Council, May 10, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 19)
- Engineering College Council, May 10-11, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 20)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 10-11, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 21)
- Ward Dinner, November 1968 (Box 109, Folder 22)
- Engineering College Council, November 8-9, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 23)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 8-9, 1968 (Box 109, Folder 24)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 14-15, 1969 (Box 109, Folder 25)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 15-16, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 1)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 20-21, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 2)
- Engineering College Council, November 21, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 3)
- Aerospace-Engineering Physics, Twentieth Anniversary Celebration, June 16-17, 1966 (Box 110, Folder 4)
- Engineering College Council - General (Box 110, Folder 5)
- Engineering College Council - General (Box 110, Folder 6)
- Engineering College Council, May 7-8, 1971 (Box 110, Folder 7)
- Engineering College Council, October 21-23, 1971 (Box 110, Folder 8)
- Engineering College Council, October 21-23, 1971 (Box 110, Folder 9)
- Engineering Convocation, October 1971 (Box 110, Folder 10)
- Engineering Convocation, October 1971 (Box 110, Folder 11)
- Engineering Convocation, October 1971 (Box 110, Folder 12)
- Engineering Convocation, October 1971 (Box 110, Folder 13)
- Engineering Convocation, October 1971 (Box 110, Folder 14)
- Engineering College Council, May 5-6, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 15)
- Engineering College Council, October 21-22, 1972 (Box 110, Folder 16)
- Engineering College Council, July 1, 1968-June 30, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 1)
- Engineering College Council, October 20-21, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 2)
- Commencement, 1972 (Box 111, Folder 3)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 11-12, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 4)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, October 5-6, 1973 (Box 111, Folder 5)
- Trustee Guidelines for College Advisory Councils, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 6)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 19-20, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 7)
- Engineering College Council Meeting- Patent Policy Discussion, April 19-20, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 8)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 8-9, 1974 (Box 111, Folder 9)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 18-19, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 10)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 7-8, 1975 (Box 111, Folder 11)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 7-8, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 12)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 19-20, 1976 (Box 111, Folder 13)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 13-14, 1977 (Box 111, Folder 14)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 11-12, 1977 (Box 111, Folder 15)
- Engineering College Council, April 21-22, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 16)
- Engineering College Council, November 3-4, 1978 (Box 111, Folder 17)
- Engineering College Council, May 4-5, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 1)
- Engineering College Council, November 16-17, 1979 (Box 112, Folder 2)
- Engineering College Council; J.F. McManus Luncheon 5/9/80, Mary 9, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 3)
- Engineering College Council, May 9-10, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 4)
- Engineering College Council; Convocation, May 9-10, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 5)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 21,22, 1980 (Box 112, Folder 6)
- Engineering College Council, 1980-1981 (Box 112, Folder 7)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, May 8-9, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 8)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, October 16-17, 1981 (Box 112, Folder 9)
- Engineering College Council - Correspondence (Box 112, Folder 10)
- Engineering College Council, 1981-1982 (Box 112, Folder 11)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 23-24, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 12)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, October 29-30, 1982 (Box 112, Folder 13)
- Engineering College Council, 1982-1983 (Box 112, Folder 14)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 8-9, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 15)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, December 2-3, 1983 (Box 112, Folder 16)
- Engineering College Council, 1983-1984 (Box 112, Folder 17)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, March 16-17, 1984 (Box 112, Folder 18)
- Engineering College Council - General, 1984-1986 (Box 113, Folder 1)
- Engineering College Council - General, 1984-1986 (Box 113, Folder 2)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 15-16, 1984 (Box 113, Folder 3)
- Engineering College Council, 1984-1985 (Box 113, Folder 4)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 19-20,1985 (Box 113, Folder 5)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, November 1-2, 1985 (Box 113, Folder 6)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, April 4-5, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 7)
- Engineering College Council Meeting, October 24-25, 1986 (Box 113, Folder 8)